eknol.blogspot.com 2018-12-19

# Privcay Policy | Blogging In Web 2.0 Beta

Computer Log Files

We use log files. Log files are those files which records the information about the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, Internet service provider (ISP), referral/exit pages, operating system, web browser, date/time, and number of clicks. This information is used to watch out the trends and analyst the statistic of blog. The log files are not linked to personally identifiable information.

User/Reader Comments

As you read our blog and may be interested to comment about our work. In this we can ask you for information like name, email or website address. We will never show your email address in public and never be sold to outside world. Not for the financial way or not for the organizational way.

Links of Other Sites

Our blog contains links to other sites. In this Case if you visit by clicking from our blog we are not responsible for any kind of the content and the privacy policy they use. Its all depends on you that you read there privacy policy or not. And also is there privacy policy is in favor of you or not. So we always recommend you to read Privacy policy of all sites you are visiting.

Advertisers

We use third party advertising companies to display advertisements on our site. These advertisements may contain cookies collected by the advertising companies, and we do not have access to this information. Please check the advertiser’s websites for their privacy policies.

Contact us for More Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please mail us at kainthblog [at] gmail.com
